Prints and Printing Slide Collection
Yale University Arts Library
- 19th – 20th Centuries (Box 6)
  - Leibl, Wilhelm, 1844-1900 (Box 7)
  - Lembruch, Wilhelm von, 1881-1919 (Box 7)
  - Liezelt, Balthazar Friedrich, act.c.1776- (Box 7)
  - Lorck, Melchior, c.1527-c.1583 (Box 7)
  - Mair Von Landshut, N.A., ac.1492-1514 (Box 7)
  - Manuel, Niklaus, c.1484-1530 (Box 7)
  - Marc, Franz, 1880-1916 [Slide box 40] (Box 7)
  - Marcks, Gerhard, 1889- (Box 7)
  - Meckenem, Isrhael van, C.1445-1503 (Box 7)
  - Menzel, Adolph, 1815-1905 (Box 7)
  - Merian, Matthias, 1593-1650 (Box 7)
  - Mitschke-Collande, C. von, 1884-1956 (Box 7)
  - Molzahn, Johannes, 1892-1965 (Box 7)
  - Mueller, Otto, 1874-1930 (Box 7)
  - Nolde, Emil, 1867-1956 (Box 7)
  - Olbrich, J.M., 1867-1908 (Box 7)
  - Oppenheim, Moritz, 1800-1882 (Box 7)
  - Orlik, Emil, 1870-1932 (Box 7)
  - Ostendorfer, M., c.1490-1559 (Box 7)
  - Overbeck, F., 1794-1854 (Box 7)
  - Pechstein, Max, 1881-1955 (Box 7)
  - Pencz, George, 1500-1550 (Box 7)
  - Polke, Sigmar, 1941- (Box 7)
  - Rethel, Alfred, 1816-1859 (Box 7)
  - Richter, Hans, 1888-1975 (Box 7)
  - Richter, Ludwig Adrian, 1803-1884 (Box 7)
  - Riemerschmid, R., 1868-1957 (Box 7)
  - Riepenhausen, Franz, 1786-1831 (Box 7)
  - Rode, Christian, 1725-1797 (Box 7)
  - Rohlfs, Christian, 1849-1938 (Box 7)
  - Runge, Philipp Otto, 1777-1810 (Box 7)
  - Schauffelin, Hans, c.1490-1539 (Box 7)
  - Schinkel, Karl F., 1781-1841 (Box 7)
  - Schmidt, Georg Friedrich, 1712-1775 (Box 7)
  - Schmidt-Rottluff, Karl, 1884-1976 (Box 7)
  - Schnorr, von Carlesfeld (Box 7)
  - Schon, Erhard, 1491? -1542 [Slide boxes 40-41] (Box 7)
  - Schonfeld, Johann, 1609-1680 [Slide box 41] (Box 7)
  - Schongauer, Martin, c.1430-1491 (Box 7)
  - Stimmer, Tobias, 1539-1584 (Box 7)
  - Stoer, Lorenz, c.1540-c.1620 (Box 7)
  - Stuck, Franz von, 1893-1928 (Box 7)
  - Traut, Wolf, c.1486-1520 (Box 7)
  - Vostell, Wolf, 1932- (Box 7)
  - Vogtherr, Heinrich (younger), 1513-1568 (Box 7)
  - Weiditz, Hans II, ac.1516-1536 (Box 7)
  - Wenzel von Olmutz, ac.1481-1497 (Box 7)
  - Winckelmann, J.J., 1717-1768 (Box 7)
  - Zainer, Johann (Box 7)
  - Zasinger, Matthaus, ac.1500 (Box 7)
- Holland (Box 7)
  - Miscellaneous Artists & Titles (Box 7)
  - 17th Century (Box 7)
    - Miscellaneous titles [Slide boxes 41-42] (Box 7)
    - Illustrations from Emblem Books [Slide box 42] (Box 7)
  - 18th Century (Box 7)
    - Illustrations from Emblem Books (Box 7)
    - Albinus, Bernard Siegfried, 1697-1770 (Box 7)
    - Backhuysen, L., 1631-1708 (Box 7)
    - Bloemart, Abraham, 1564-1651 (Box 7)
    - Blondel, J. F., 1705-1774 (Box 7)
    - Bol, Ferdinand, 1616-c.1580 (Box 7)
    - Both, Jan, 1618-1652 (Box 7)
    - Brune, Johan de (Box 7)
      Prints Holland, see Veen, J. van der
    - Buytewech, Willem, 1585-1627 (Box 7)
    - Claez, Allaert, 1498-1564 (Box 7)
    - Claez, Pieter, 1597-1661 (Box 7)
    - Cock, Hieronymus, 1510-1570 (Box 7)
    - Dujardin, Karel, 1622-1678 (Box 7)
    - Escher, Maurits Cornelis, 1898-1972 (Box 7)
    - Everdingen, Allaert van, 1621-1675 (Box 7)
    - Gheyn, Jacob van, 1565-1629 (Box 7)
    - Goltzius, Hendrik, 1558-1617 [Slide boxes 42-43] (Box 7–8)
    - Hals, Franz, 1580-1666 [Slide box 43] (Box 8)
    - Hameel, Allaert du, 1449-1509 (Box 8)
    - Heemskerck, Martin, 1498-1574 (Box 8)
    - Holst, Roland, 1869-? (Box 8)
    - Hooghe, Roman de, 1645-1708 (Box 8)
    - Hondius, Hendrick I., 1573-1649 (Box 8)
    - Humbert de Superville, 1770-1849 (Box 8)
    - Huszar, Vilmos, 1884-1960 (Box 8)
    - Kittensteyn, Cornelis van, ac.1600-1638 (Box 8)
    - Kinderen, A.J. der, 1859-1925 (Box 8)
    - Koninck, Philip de, 1619-1688 (Box 8)
    - Lairesse, Gerard de, 1641-1711 (Box 8)
    - Lastman, Pieter, 1583-1633 (Box 8)
    - Lievens, Jan 1607-1674 (Box 8)
    - Lucas Van Leyden, 1494-1533 (Box 8)
    - Mathan, Jacob, 1571-1631 (Box 8)
    - Moucheron, Isaac de, 1667-1744 (Box 8)
    - Ostade, Adriaen van, 1610-1685 (Box 8)
    - Passe, Crispyn de, 1564-1637 (Box 8)
    - Potter, Paul, 1625-1654 (Box 8)
    - Prikker, J.T., 1868-1932 (Box 8)
    - Rademaker, Abraham, 1675-1735 (Box 8)
    - Rembrandt Van Rijin, 1606-1669 (Box 8)
      - Miscellaneous Titles (Box 8)
      - Genre (Box 8)
      - Landscapes [Slide boxes 43-44] (Box 8)
      - Portraits [Slide box 44] (Box 8)
        - Self Portraits (Box 8)
      - Religious (Box 8)
        - Abraham Entertaining the Angels (Box 8)
        - Abraham's Sacrifice (Box 8)
        - Adoration of Shepherds (Box 8)
        - Angel appearing to the Angels (Box 8)
        - Christ and the Money Charges (Box 8)
        - Christ & Woman of Samaria (Box 8)
        - Christ Healing the Sick (100 guilder) [Slide boxes 44-45] (Box 8)
        - Christ Preaching [Slide box 45] (Box 8)
        - Christ Presented to the People (Box 8)
        - Descent from Cross (Box 8)
        - Entombment (Box 8)
        - Flight into Egypt (Box 8)
        - Good Samaritan (Box 8)
        - Night Nativity (Box 8)
        - Presentation in Temple (Box 8)
        - Raising of Lazarus (Box 8)
        - Return of Prodigal Son (Box 8)
        - S. Jerome (Box 8)
        - The Three Crosses (Box 8)
        - Triumph of Mordecai (Box 8)
    - Ruysdael, Jacob van, c.1629-1682 (Box 8)
    - Seghers, Hercules, c.1590-c.1640 [Slide boxes 45-46] (Box 8)
    - Suyderhouf, Jonas, 1613-1686 [Slide box 46] (Box 8)
    - Swanvelt, Herman, 1600-1655 (Box 8)
    - Swart Jan Van G., 1500-1553 (Box 8)
    - Thorn-Prikker, Jan, 1868-1932 (Box 8)
    - Toorop, Jan, 1858-1928 (Box 8)
    - Uyttenbroeck, Moysesz van, c.1590-1684 (Box 8)
    - Van Gogh, Vincent, 1853-1890 (Box 8)
    - Veen, J. Van Der (Box 8)
    - Velde, Esias van de, 1951-1630 (Box 8)
    - Velde, Jan Van de, 1593-1641 (Box 8)
    - Velde, Jan Van de (III) (Box 8)
    - Visscher, Roemer (Box 8)
      For Prints Holland, see Veen, J. van der
    - Vredeman de Vries, Hans (Jan), 1526-1606 (Box 8)
    - Waterloo. Anthonie, c.1610-1690 (Box 8)
    - Wijck, Thomas, c.1616-1677 (Box 8)
    - Witsen, Nicholas, ac.1785 (Box 8)
- Hungary (Box 8)
  - Moholy-Nagy, Laszlo, 1895-1946 (Box 8)
- India (Box 8)
  - Miscellaneous Titles (Box 8)
- Italy (Box 8)
  - 15th Century (Box 8)
    - Miscellaneous Titles (Box 8)
  - 16th Century [Slide box 47] (Box 8)
    - Miscellaneous Titles (Box 8)
  - 17th Century (Box 8)
    - Miscellaneous Titles (Box 8)
    - La Carta del Navegar Pitoresco, 1660 (Box 8)
  - 18th Century (Box 8)
    For Title page and views from Bianchini see Arch. Renaissance Italy, Florence General
    - Aldus Manutius, printer [Slide boxes 47-48] (Box 8)
    - Andrea, Zoan, c.1475-1505 [Slide box 48] (Box 8)
    - Arcimboldo, Giuseppe (Box 8)
    - Bandinelli, Baccio (after) (Box 8)
    - Barbari, Jacopi di, 1450-1516 (Box 8)
      For view plan of Venice, 1500, see Architecture Renaissance Italy Venice
    - Barbiere, Domenico, 1506-1565 (Box 8)
    - Barocci, F., 1526-1612 (Box 8)
    - Bartolozzi, Francesco, 1727-1815 (Box 8)
    - Beccafumi, D., 1486-1551 (Box 8)
    - Bella, Stefano Della, 1610-1664 (Box 8)
    - Belloto, Bernardo, 1720-1780 (Box 8)
    - Boccione, Umberto, 1882-1916 (Box 8)
    - Boldrini, Nicolo (Box 8)
    - Bonasone, Giulio, c.1498-1580 (Box 8)
    - Borgianni, Orazio, 1578-1616 (Box 8)
    - Botticelli (after) (Box 8)
    - Bracello, G.B., ac.1616-1649 (Box 8)
    - Caletti, Giuseppe, 1600-1691 (Box 8)
    - Campagnola, Domenico, 1482-1562 (Box 8)
    - Campagnola, Giulio, 1482-1515 (Box 8)
    - Canal, Antonio, 1697-1768 (Box 8)
      Also know as Canaletto
    - Cantagallina, Remigio, c.1585-1656 (Box 8)
      For Prints of Stage Design, see Stage Design Italy, Parigi, Giulio
    - Cappiello, L., 1875-1942 (Box 8)
    - Caravaggio, 1571-1610 (Box 8)
    - Carpi, Ugo da, c.1479-1532 (Box 8)
    - Carra, Carlo, 1881-1966 (Box 8)
    - Carraci, Agostino, 1557-1602 (Box 8)
      For Prints of Stage Design, see –Stage Design Italy—Buontalenti, Bernardo
    - Carraci, Annibale, 1560-1609 (Box 8)
    - Castiglione, G.B., 1616-1670 (Box 8)
    - Cipriani, G.B., 1727-1785/90 (Box 8)
    - Clemente, Francesco, 1952- (Box 8)
    - Cohn, Tobias, 1652-1729 (Box 8)
    - Faccini, Pietro, 1562-1602 (Box 8)
    - Fantuzzi, Antonio, c.1508-1550 (Box 8)
    - Fattori, Giovanni, 1825-1908 (Box 8)
    - Fialetti, Odoardo, 1573-1638 (Box 8)
    - Finiguerra, Maso, 1426-1464 (Box 8)
    - Ghisi, Giogio, c.1520-1582 (Box 8)
    - Giulio, Romano, 1499-1546 [Slide boxes 48-49] (Box 8–9)
    - Giraldi, Lilio Gregorio, 1479-1552 [Slide box 49] (Box 9)
    - Lafrery, Antoine, 1512-1580 (Box 9)
    - Lana, Ludovico, 1597-1646 (Box 9)
    - Leoni, Ottavio M., 1578-1630 (Box 9)
    - Leonardis, Jacopo, 1723-1782 (Box 9)
    - Mantegna, Andrea, 1431-1506 (Box 9)
      For Comparison Foreshortened, see—Miscelaneous Perspective—Photograph, foreshortened football player
    - Marinetti, F.T., 1876-1944 (Box 9)
      Also know as Marineti, (Emilio) Filippo
    - Martini, Pietro A., 1739-1797 (Box 9)
    - Master of the Tarocchi, act. C.1465- (Box 9)
    - Michelangelo (after) (Box 9)
    - Mitelli, G.M., 1634-1718 (Box 9)
    - Mocetto, Girolamo, 1458-1531 (Box 9)
    - Morandi, Giorgio, 1890-1964 (Box 9)
    - Paladino, Mimmo, 1948- (Box 9)
    - Parmigianino, 1503-1540 (Box 9)
    - Penni, Luca, 1500-1556 (Box 9)
    - Piranesi, Francesco (Box 9)
    - Piranesi, G.B., 1720-1778 (Box 9)
      See also Painting Italy
      - Miscellaneous Titles (Box 9)
      - Antichita Romane (Box 9)
      - Campo Marzio [Slide box 50] (Box 9)
      - Diverse Maniere (Box 9)
      - Prima Parte… (Box 9)
      - Prisons (carceri) (Box 9)
      - Thoughts on Architecture… (Box 9)
      - Vedute di Roma (Box 9)
    - Pollaiulo, A., 1433-1498 (Box 9)
    - Prevedari, B., 15th Century (Box 9)
    - Primaticcio, Francesco, 1504-1570 (Box 9)
    - Raimondi, Marcan., 1480-1527 (Box 9)
      Also known as Raimondi, Marcantonio
      For additional engravings –under Prints Italy—Raphael Giulio Romano
    - Raphael Sanzio, 1483-1520 (Box 9)
      - Miscellaneous Titles (Box 9)
      - By Bonase [Slide box 51] (Box 9)
      - By Ghisi (Box 9)
      - By Raimondi (Box 9)
      - By Vico (Box 9)
    - Reni, Guido, 1575-1642 (Box 9)
    - Rippa, Matteo S.J., 1682-1746 (Box 9)
    - Rosa, Salvator, 1615-1673 (Box 9)
    - Rosselli, Francesco, 1448-1513 (Box 9)
    - Rosso Fiorentino, 1494-1540 (Box 9)
      Also know as Rosso Fiorentino (Giovanni) or Il Rosso
    - Rota, Martino, 1520-1583 (Box 9)
    - Scolari, Giuseppe (Box 9)
    - Soffici, Ardengo, 1879-1964 (Box 9)
    - Tiepolo, Giovanni B.1696-1770 [Slide box 52] (Box 9)
    - Tiepolo, G.D., 1727-1804 (Box 9)
    - Titian, 1477-1576 (Box 9)
    - Trevisani, Francesco, 1656-1746 (Box 9)
    - Vasari, Giorgio, 1511-1574 (Box 9)
    - Vecellio, Cesare, ca.1521-1601 (Box 9)
    - Vico, Enea, 1520-1563/7 (Box 9)
    - Villamena, Francesco, 1566-1624 (Box 9)
    - Zoan, Andrea, ca.1475-1515 (Box 9)
    - Zocchi, Giuseppe, 1711-1767 (Box 9)
- New Zealand (Box 9)
  - Angas, George French, 1822-1886 (Box 9)
- Norway (Box 9)
  - Munch, Edvard, 1863-1944 (Box 9)
    - Miscellaneous Titles [Slide boxes 52-53] (Box 9)
    - The Kiss [Slide box 53] (Box 9)
- Poland (Box 9)
  - Various Artists (Box 9)
- Portugal (Box 9)
  - Hollanda Francisco de, 1517-1584 (Box 9)
- Romania (Box 9)
  - Janko, Marcel, 1895- (Box 9)
- Russia (Box 9)
  - Miscellaneous Artists (Box 9)
  - Chagall, Marc, 1887-1985 (Box 9)
  - Ermolaeva, V. (Box 9)
  - Gontcharova, Natalia, 1881-1962 (Box 9)
  - Guminer, Yakov (Box 9)
  - Kandinsky, Wassily, 1866-1944 (Box 9)
  - Klutsis, Gustave, 1895-1944 (Box 9)
  - Kulbin, N (Box 9)
  - Lavinsky, Anton, 1893-1968 (Box 9)
    X Lavinskij, Anton
  - Lissitzky, El, 1890-1941 (Box 9)
    - Various Titles [Slide boxes 53-54] (Box 9)
    - Pronoun Portfolio [Slide box 54] (Box 9)
    - Story of Two Squares (Box 9)
    - Victory over the Sun (Box 9)
  - Malevich, Kasimir, 1878-1935 (Box 9)
  - Prusakov & Borisov (Box 9)
  - Rodchenko, Alex, 1891-1956 [Slide boxes 54-55] (Box 9–10)
    X Rodchenko, Aexandre
    X Rodcenko, Aleksandr Mihailovi
  - Semenova, Elena, 1898-1986 (Box 10)
  - Stepanova, Elena, 1894-1958 (Box 10)
  - Stenberg, Georgi & Vladimir (Box 10)
- Spain (Box 10)
  - Miscellaneous Artists (Box 10)
  - Goya, Francisco, 1746-1828 (Box 10)
    - Various Titles (Box 10)
    - Caprichos (Box 10)
    - The Disasters of War (Box 10)
    - Proverbs (Box 10)
    - Tauromaquia [Slide boxes 55-56] (Box 10)
  - Picasso, Pablo, 1881-1973 [Slide box 56] (Box 10)
    - Various Titles (Box 10)
    - The Blind Minotaur (Box 10)
    - The Minotaur (Box 10)
    - Sculptor's Studio (Box 10)
    - Suite 347 (Box 10)
  - Ribera, Jusepe, 1588-1652 (Box 10)
- Sweden (Box 10)
  - Eggelin, Vicking, 1886-1925 (Box 10)
  - Zorn, Anders L., 1860-1920 (Box 10)
- Switzerland (Box 10)
  - Various Artists (Box 10)
  - Bodmer, Karl, 1809-1893 [Slide box 57] (Box 10)
  - Klee, Paul, 1879-1940 (Box 10)
  - Vallotton, Felix, 1865-1925 (Box 10)
- Latin America (Box 10)
  - Various Countries (Box 10)
  - Argentina (Box 10)
  - Brazil (Box 10)
  - Uruguay (Box 10)
  - Venezuela (Box 10)
  - Mexico (Box 10)
    - Miscellaneous Artists (Box 10)
    - Charlot, Jean, 1891- (Box 10)
    - De Molina, Alonso, ac.c.1565 (Box 10)
    - Mendez, Leopoldo, 1903-1934 (Box 10)
    - Orozco, Gabriel, 1962- (Box 10)
    - Posada, Jose Guadalupe., 1851-1913 (Box 10)
    - Valades, Diego de, 1533-1582 (Box 10)
      X Valades, Fray Diego de
  - United States (Box 10)
    - 18th Century (Box 10)
      - Various Titles [Slide boxes 57-58] (Box 10)
    - 19th Century (Box 10)
      - Various Artists & Titles (Box 10)
      - Afro-American Subjects (Box 10)
    - 20th Century (Box 10)
      - Various Titles (Box 10)
      - Little Magazines (Box 10)
        - Critique (Box 10)
        - Dyn (Box 10)
        - It Is (Box 10)
        - The Masses [Slide boxes 58-59] (Box 10)
        - Modern Artists in America [Slide box 59] (Box 10)
        - Possibilities (Box 10)
        - Tiger's Eye (Box 10)
        - VVV (Box 10)
        - View (Box 10)
      - Abelman, Ida, 1910- (Box 10)
      - Albers, Josef, 1888-1976 (Box 10)
        - Various Titles (Box 10)
        - Multiplex (Box 10)
        - Structural Constellation (Box 10)
        - Transformations of a Scheme [Slide boxes 59-60] (Box 10)
      - Albright, Ivan, 1897- [Slide box 60] (Box 10)
      - Arai, Tomie, 1949- (Box 10)
      - Artschwager, Richard, 1924- (Box 10)
      - Audobon, John James, 1785-1874 (Box 10)
      - Bacon, F. & Taylor, J.W. (Box 10)
      - Bacon, Peggy (Box 10)
      - Baranik, Rudolf, 1920- (Box 10)
      - Barralet, J.J., c.1747-1815 (Box 10)
      - Baskin, Leonard, 1922- (Box 10)
      - Beal, Jack, 1931- (Box 10)
      - Becker, Fred, 1913- (Box 10)
      - Bellows, George, 1882-1925 (Box 10)
      - Bennett, William, 1777-1844 (Box 10)
      - Benton, Thomas H., 1889- (Box 10)
      - Bingham, George Caleb (Box 10)
      - Birch, William Russell & Son Thomas, 1755-1834 (Box 10)
      - Bishop, Isabel, 1902- (Box 10)
      - Blackburn, Robert, 1920- (Box 10)
      - Blum, Robert, 1857-1903 (Box 10)
      - Blythe, David Gilmore (Box 10)
      - Bodmer, Karl, 1809-1893 (Box 10)
      - Boetticher, Otto (Box 10)
      - Broner, Robert, 1922- (Box 10)
      - Brown, M.E.D., ac.1832-1896 (Box 10)
      - Brown, William H., 1808-1883 (Box 10)
      - Browning, Colleen (Box 10)
      - Burck, Jacob, 1904- (Box 10)
      - Burgis, William, act.c.1715-1731 (Box 10)
      - Cadmus, Paul, 1904- (Box 10)
      - Calder, Alexander, 1898- (Box 10)
      - Cassatt, Mary, 1845-1926 (Box 10)
      - Castellon, Frederico [Slide box 61] (Box 11)
      - Catlett, Elizabeth, 1915- (Box 11)
      - Catlin, George, 1796-1872 (Box 11)
      - Chaney, Ruth, 1908- (Box 11)
      - Chapman, John Gadsby, 1808-1889 (Box 11)
      - Chesney, Lee, 1920- (Box 11)
      - Church, Frederick, 1826-1900 (Box 11)
      - Clay, Edward W., 1792-1857 (Box 11)
      - Clements, Grace R., 1905- (Box 11)
      - Close, Chuck, 1940- (Box 11)
      - Cole, J.F.A. (Box 11)
      - Cole, Thomas, 1801-1848 (Box 11)
      - Cook, Howard, 1901- (Box 11)
      - Copley, John Singleton, 1738-1815 (Box 11)
      - Currier & Ives, 1834-1907 [Slide boxes 61-62] (Box 11)
      - Curry, John Steuart [Slide box 62] (Box 11)
      - Darley, Felix, 1822-1888 (Box 11)
      - Davies, Arthur, 1862-1928 (Box 11)
      - Davis, Stuart, 1894-1964 (Box 11)
      - Dawkins, Henry, ac.1753-1786 (Box 11)
      - Denn, Adolf, 1895- (Box 11)
      - Deshaies, Arthur, 1920- (Box 11)
      - Dine, Jim, 1935- (Box 11)
      - Doolittle, Amos, 1754-1832 (Box 11)
      - Douglas, Aaron, 1898-1978 (Box 11)
        For Comparison Africa Central – Mangbetu woman
      - Durand, Asher Brown, 1796-1886 (Box 11)
      - Duval, George (Box 11)
      - Duveneck, Frank, 1848-1919 (Box 11)
      - Eichenberg, Fritz, 1901- (Box 11)
      - Estes, Richard, 1936- (Box 11)
      - Feininger, Lyonel, 1871-1956 (Box 11)
      - Fischl, Eric, 1948- (Box 11)
      - Flack, Audrey, 1931- (Box 11)
      - Forbes, Edwin, 1839-1895 (Box 11)
      - Foster, John, 1648-1681 (Box 11)
      - Frank, Regina, 1965- (Box 11)
      - Franklin, Benjamin, 1706-1790 (Box 11)
      - Frasconi, Antoni, 1919- (Box 11)
      - Freeman, Don, 1908-1978 (Box 11)
      - Fuller, Sue (Box 11)
      - Gag, Wanda, 1893-1946 (Box 11)
      - Gibson, Charles Dana (Box 11)
      - Gonzalez-Torres, Felix, 1957- (Box 11)
      - Gorelick, Boris, 20th Century (Box 11)
      - Gottlieb, Harry, 1895- (Box 11)
      - Graham, Curtis Burr, c.1815-1890 [Slide box 63] (Box 11)
      - Grambs, Blanche, 1916- (Box 11)
      - Greenwood, John, 1727-1792 (Box 11)
      - Gridley, Enoch, ac.1803-1818 (Box 11)
      - Griggs, F.L. (Box 11)
      - Grooms, Red (Box 11)
      - Gropper, William, 1897-1977 (Box 11)
      - Grozelier, Leopold, 1830-1865 (Box 11)
      - Guerrilla Girls, 1985- (Box 11)
      - Gysin, Brion, 1916-1986 (Box 11)
      - Hammons, David, 1943- (Box 11)
      - Haring, Keith, 1958-1990 (Box 11)
      - Harnett, William M., 1848-1892 (Box 11)
      - Hart, George O., 1868-1933 (Box 11)
      - Hassam, Childe, 1859-1935 (Box 11)
      - Havell, Robert Jr., 1793-1878 (Box 11)
      - Helfold, Riva, 1910- (Box 11)
      - Hendricks, Jon, 1940- (Box 11)
      - Hernandez, Ester, 1944- (Box 11)
      - Hill, Clinton, 1922- (Box 11)
      - Hill, John, 1770-1850 (Box 11)
      - Hirsch, Joseph, 1910- (Box 11)
      - Holzer, Jenny (Box 11)
      - Homer, Winslow, 1836-1910 (Box 11)
      - Hopper, Edward, 1882-1967 (Box 11)
      - Hunt, William Morris, 1824-1879 (Box 11)
      - Hurd, Nathaniel, 1729-1777 (Box 11)
      - Indiana, Robert, 1928- (Box 11)
      - Inman, Henry, 1801-1846 (Box 11)
      - Jennings, Wilmer, 1910- (Box 11)
      - Johns, Jasper, 1930- [Slide boxes 63-64] (Box 11)
      - Johnson, Sargent Claude, 1887-1965 [Slide box 64] (Box 11)
      - Johnson, Eastman, 1824-1906 (Box 11)
      - Johnston, David Claypoole, 1797-1865 (Box 11)
      - Johnston, Thomas, c.1708-1767 (Box 11)
      - Jones-Hogu, Barbara, 1938- (Box 11)
      - Jordon, Raymond, 1898- (Box 11)
      - Kainen, Jacob, 1909- (Box 11)
      - Katz, Alex, 1927- (Box 11)
      - Kent, Rockwell, 1882- (Box 11)
      - Kepets, Hugh (Box 11)
      - Koppelman, Chaim (Box 11)
      - Krimmel, John Lewis (Box 11)
      - Kuniyoshi, Yasuo (Box 11)
      - Kupferman, Lawrance, 1909- (Box 11)
      - Kurz & Allison, act.c.1880-1890 (Box 11)
      - Landeck, Armin, 1905- (Box 11)
      - Lasansky, Mauricio (Box 11)
      - Lawrence, Jacob, 1917- (Box 11)
      - Lawson, Alexander, 1773-1846 (Box 11)
      - Lebrun, Rico, 1900- (Box 11)
      - Lehman, George (Box 11)
        X Lehman & Duval
      - Lewis, Martin (Box 11)
      - Lewitt, Sol, 1928- (Box 11)
      - Lichtenstein, Roy, 1923- (Box 11)
      - Limbach, Russell, 1904- (Box 11)
      - Lion, Jules, c.1810-1866 (Box 11)
      - Lobdell, Frank (Box 11)
      - Longo, Robert, 1953- (Box 11)
      - Lozowick, Louis, 1892-1973 (Box 11)
      - Ludenberg, Helen, 1908- (Box 11)
      - MacDonald-Wright, Stanton, 1890-1973 (Box 11)
      - Maciunas, George (Box 11)
      - Marden, Brice, 1938- (Box 11)
      - Marin, John, 1890-1953 (Box 11)
      - Marisol, 1930- (Box 11)
      - Marsh, Reginald, 1898-1954 [Slide boxes 64-65] (Box 11)
      - Martin, Agnes, 1911- [Slide box 65] (Box 11)
      - Mesibov, Hubert, 1916- (Box 11)
      - Moorhead, Scipio (Box 11)
      - Moran, Thomas (Box 11)
      - Morgan, Norma (Box 11)
      - Morley, Eugene, 1909- (Box 11)
      - Motherwell, Robert, 1915- (Box 11)
      - Morris, Robert, 1931- (Box 11)
      - Mount, William Sidney, 1807-1868 (Box 11)
      - Moy, Seong (Box 11)
      - Murphy, Arthur (Box 11)
      - Nast, Thomas, 1840-1902 (Box 11)
      - Nelson, Joan (Box 11)
      - Nevelson, Louise, 1899- (Box 11)
      - Newsam, Albert (Box 11)
      - Oakford Ellen (Box 11)
        Xx for Elm Arcade, 1889 New Haven, see Arch. U.S. New Haven Gen. Views Temple Street
      - Oldenburg, Claes, 1929- (Box 11)
      - Olds, Elizabeth, 1896- (Box 11)
      - Otis, Bass, 1784-1861 (Box 11)
      - Palmer, F.F., c.1812-1876 (Box 11)
      - Parsons, Charles, 1821-1910 (Box 11)
      - Peale, Charles Wilson, 1741-1827 (Box 11)
      - Peale, James Jr., 1789-1876 (Box 11)
      - Peale, Rembrandt, 1788-1860 (Box 11)
      - Peale, Titian (after) (Box 11)
      - Pearlstein, Philip, 1924- (Box 11)
      - Pelham, Henry, 1749-1806 (Box 11)
      - Pelham, Peter, c.1684-1751 (Box 11)
      - Pennell, Joseph, 1857-1926 (Box 11)
      - Platt, Charles A., 1861-1933 (Box 11)
      - Pollock, Jackson, 1912-1956 (Box 11)
      - Pozzatti, Rudy (Box 11)
      - Predergast, M., 1859-1924 (Box 11)
      - Pytlak, Leonard, 1910- (Box 11)
      - Queen, Walker & Duval (Box 11)
      - Racz, Andre, 1916- (Box 11)
      - Rauschenberg, Robert, 1925- (Box 11)
      - Reason, Patrick H., 1817-1898 [Slide box 66] (Box 11)
      - Reder, Bernard, 1897- (Box 11)
      - Remington, Frederic, 1861-1909 (Box 11)
      - Revere, Paul, 1735-1818 (Box 11)
      - Rimmer, Wiliam, 1816-1879 (Box 11)
      - Rivers, Larry, 1923- (Box 11)
      - Rosenquist, James, 1933- (Box 11)
      - Ruscha, Edward, 1937- (Box 11)
      - Ryan, Anne (Box 11)
      - Sanchez, Juan, 1954- (Box 11)
      - Sargent, John Singer, 1856-1925 (Box 11)
      - Savage, Edward, 1761-1817 (Box 11)
      - Schanker, Louis, 1903- (Box 11)
      - Scholder, Fritz (Box 11)
      - Schwartz, William S., 1896-1977 (Box 11)
      - Shahn, Ben, 1898- (Box 11)
      - Shapiro, Joel, 1941- (Box 11)
      - Sheeler, Charles, 1883- (Box 11)
      - Sloan, John, 1871-1951 (Box 11)
      - Smillie, James, 1807-1885 (Box 11)
      - Smith, David, 1906-1965 (Box 11)
      - Smith, John R., 1770-1849 (Box 11)
      - Smith, Kiki, 1954- (Box 11)
      - Soyer, Raphael, 1899- (Box 11)
      - Spero, Nancy, 1926- (Box 11)
      - Steffen, Bernard J., 1907- (Box 11)
      - Stella, Frank, 1936- (Box 11)
      - Sternberg, Harry, 1904- (Box 11)
      - Summers, Carol, 1925- (Box 11)
      - Tait, Arthur F. (Box 11)
      - Taskey, Harry L., 1892-1958 (Box 11)
      - Thompson, Thomas (Box 11)
      - Tobey, Mark, 1890-1976 (Box 11)
      - Thrash, Dox, 1893- (Box 11)
      - Trumbull, John, 1756-1843 (Box 11)
      - Turzak, Charles, 1899- [Slide box 67] (Box 12)
      - Twatchtman, John, 1853-1902 (Box 12)
      - Twombly, Cy, 1929- (Box 12)
      - Vanderlyn, John (after) (Box 12)
      - Vassos, John (Box 12)
      - Velonis, Antony, 1911- (Box 12)
      - Vogel, Joseph, 1911- (Box 12)
      - Wald, Sylvia (Box 12)
      - Walton, Henry (Box 12)
      - Warhol, Andy, 1928-1987 (Box 12)
        Xx Film U.S. & Painting U.S.
        - Miscellaneous Titles (Box 12)
        - Book Illustrations (Box 12)
        - Poster (Box 12)
        - Record Cover (Box 12)